麦克斯 这是我们甜品吧的油漆颜色图
Okay, Max, here are the paint chips for our new dessert bar.
别吃掉 这不是你的童年
Don't eat them. This isn't your childhood.
全都是粉色
These are all pink.
你希望我们甜品吧的墙是粉色吗
You want the walls of our bar to be all pink?
来店里喝酒顾客大概会是
It'll be the first time someone drinks
史上首次进"阴道"里喝酒的人吧
after they enter a vagina.
餐厅里不许出现"阴道"二字
Oh, hey... no vagina in the dina.
你的公寓里也没有出现过"阴道"
Or your apartment. Ever.
这里不是女服务员卖肉餐厅
You know, this isn't Hooters.
那种字眼通常不会随便出现在公共场合
The v-bomb isn't usually batted around the workplace.
说到随便出现
Speaking of batting things around,
我家喵星人想你再来一趟
our cat wants you to come over again.
昨天你才说你家喵星人
Yesterday you said your cat
太霸气 不屑与我为伍
was too cool to hang out with me.
所以到底是怎么样
So which is it?
因为我今晚还真的有空
'Cause I am free tonight.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
你们知道今天是什么日子吗
You know what today is?
希望不是15号
I hope it ain't the 15th,
因为那意味着我错过做透析了
'cause that means I missed dialysis.
不是啦 是我怀孕满20周了
No, I'm 20 weeks preggers.
是时候我和奥列格为孩子选干爹妈了
And it's time for Oleg and I to choose the godparents.
这是我们波兰的一个老传统之一
You know, it's an old Polish tradition.
就像波兰饺子与绞刑示众
Like pierogies and public hangings.
干爹妈[上帝父母]吗
Godparents?
上帝连真的爹妈都没给过我
God didn't even give me parents-parents.
他只给了我用影带出租店塑料袋
He just gave me some lady that took me home from the hospital
把我从医院装回家的女人
in a Blockbuster Video bag.
这是个重大决定
It's a big decision.
因为你得选一对跟你有相同信仰与价值观的
You have to pick a couple who would raise the child
夫妇来当干爹妈
with your beliefs and values.
但《花花公子》的老板和他的小蜜
And Hugh Hefner and whoever he's banging
已经拒绝了我们
already said no.
所以我在列张候选人表
Yeah, so I'm making a list.
但奥列格不想要在监狱的人
But Oleg doesn't want anyone in prison.
所以我家族里的女人基本都被淘汰出局了
You know, so that knocks out most of the women in my family.
你们俩也可以在家
You know, you guys could also have
讨论这些话题啊
these conversations at home.
但这个台子就是他们造人的地方
But this counter is where they made the baby.
你好啊 厄尔
Hey, Earl.
太好了 我正需要一名壮汉帮忙
Oh, good, I need somebody strong.
能麻烦你把这个搬到那里
Uh, would you carry this over there,
然后往里面加点咖啡
put some coffee in it,
然后再搬回来给我吗
and bring it back to me?
我很快就帮你搞定
I'll hot this up in a second.
先等我把这妞搞定就行
Just let me hot this one up first.
你来干嘛呢
What're you doing here?
我知道你不喜欢我在你闲暇时间烦你
I know you don't like me to bother you during your free time,
但我想你了
but I missed you.
而且我有事情想当面对你说
And I want to tell you something in person.
无论是什么"病" 我估计也有
Well, whatever it is, I probably have it too.
而且估计比你早就染上了
And I probably had it first.
不是这种事
It's not that.
但你说完我开始担心了
But now I'm worried.
我跟一家在曼哈顿的律师事务所谈了
No, I met with this law firm in Manhattan,
他们想让我成为合伙人
and they want to make me a partner.
他们要让你成为合伙人[伴侣]吗
They're making you a partner?
那估计他们也会"染上"了
Well, then they're gonna catch it too.
兰迪
So, Randy,
你真的是律师啊
you really are a lawyer?
我还以为你只是在基佬黄片里演过律师
I thought you just played lawyers in gay porn.
谢谢
Thanks.
我会告诉我的健身教练
I will tell my trainer.
他倒是真拍过基佬黄片
He was in gay porn.
巴斯光年
Hey, Buzz Lightyear,
我还在等那杯咖啡呢
I'm still waiting for that coffee.
好啦 我去我的卡座坐了
All right, well, I'll be in my booth
继续弄我的干爹妈列表
working on my godparent list.
我们最后选的人
And whoever we pick should be like one of those
一定会像电视上的完美家庭 比如《脱线家族》
perfect families on TV like, well, the Brady's,
《天才老爹》
and the Huxtables...
算了 最后这部不要[主角为黑人一家]
Or, you know what? Scratch that last one.
如果你真的考虑要搬来纽约
Wow, if you're considering moving to New York,
那个工作铁定很不错吧
it must be a pretty good job.
还有一些其他原因
Well, there's a couple other reasons.
好吃的百吉饼
The bagels.
百老汇音乐剧《汉密尔顿》七年的票
I have tickets to Hamilton in seven years.
外加这里有个我还算喜欢的姑娘
And there's this girl here I kind of like.
她是谁 我去宰了她
Who is she? I'll kill her.
其中两个合伙人明晚想带我
So two of the partners want to take me out tomorrow night
去一家名叫"喙"的高档私人餐厅
to some fancy private dinner at someplace called Beak.
你要去"喙"吗
You're going to Beak?
这餐厅隐藏在一间私人公寓里
It's hidden away in a private apartment,
就在威廉斯堡大桥的下方
practically under the Williamsburg Bridge,
所以基本上得走去
so you pretty much have to walk.
真是太糟糕太时髦了
How awful and chic is that?
我在杂志上读到 那地方特隐秘
I read in Time Out that that place is so exclusive,
基本上都算不上是家餐厅了
it's technically not even a restaurant.
有啥了不起
Big deal.
这家餐厅也总被人说"算不上餐厅"啊
This diner gets called "Not a restaurant" all the time.
他们有说只能带麦克斯吗
Hey, did they tell you to just bring Max,
还是随便你带人
or was it more of a "bring whoever"?
我就当是可以随便带人了
I'll take that as a yes.
我十分乐意明天加入你们在"喙"的晚餐
I'd love to join you at Beak tomorrow night.
我怎么拒绝的了"喙"的诱惑
How could I say no to Beak?
春日时光 "喙"
It's spring, so that's peak Beak.
你想去吗
So you want to go?
想当我的女伴吗
Want to be my date?
表要 我不去
Nah, pass.
三样我不愿意干的事情中 高档餐厅是一样
Fancy restaurants are one of the three things I don't do.
另外两样你懂的
You know the other two.
我们不是第一周的时候就全"干"了吗
Didn't we blow past those week one?
麦克斯 你疯了吗
Max, are you crazy?
为啥 我的其中一个瞳孔又缩小了吗
Why, is one of my pupils getting all small?
它现在无缘无故就这样 我也不知道为什么
It happens now. I don't know why.
你刚才是在干嘛
What was that out there?
"表要 我不去"
"Nah, pass."
兰迪不仅仅是单纯邀请你去吃饭
Randy's not just asking you to dinner-dinner.
重点不是食物
This isn't about food.
是你们在一起的未来
It's about your future together.
他要为你搬来这里
He's moving here for you.
而你说"表要 我不去"拒绝了兰迪
You just "Naw pass" -ed on Randy.
怪了 你第一次模仿我时我不喜欢
Weird, I didn't love your impression the first time,
但第二次我超喜欢呢
but I loved it the second.
兰迪搬来是因为工作
Randy's moving here for a job.
这顿饭主题不是什么律师合伙人
This dinner isn't about some law partners.
而是你和他要"合伙"了
It's about you and him as partners.
是我有漏听他说了什么话吗
Do you hear words I don't?
那顿晚餐你必须得去 小姑娘
You're going to that dinner, young lady,
别争了
end of discussion.
这话好有妈妈范儿啊
Oh, that was so mom-ish!
我不知道 我没见过妈
I wouldn't know. I've never met one.
太好了 是这里
Oh, good, this is it.
我们敲错了另一家的门
We knocked on another apartment door,
他们唯一在做的东西是冰毒
but the only thing they were cooking was meth.
我们徒步走过大桥就为了这个吗
We walked across a bridge for this?
这跟我的公寓唯一差别是
This is basically my apartment,
我家的野鸟都是活的
except our wild birds are alive.
兰迪 你成功啦
Randy, you made it.
不是说功成名就 是说你成功能在这吃饭
And I mean, you made it because you're eating at Beak.
排队要吃这里的名单
I mean, the wait list here is longer
比又臭又长的HBO剧《黑胶时代》还长
than an episode of HBO's Vinyl.
麦克斯 这位是玛丽莎 其中一位合伙人
Max, this is Marissa, one of the partners.
玛丽莎 这位是麦克斯
Marissa, this is Max.
她是我女朋友
She's my girlfriend.
麦克斯吗 这名字挺好
Max? Cute.
是麦克儿欣恩的短称吗
Is that short for Maxine?
其实应该是"咩"的长称
Technically, it's long for "Meh."
抱歉 没懂你意思
Sorry, I don't get it.
可能是我吃了镇静剂
Probably because of the Klonopin I had to take
因为刚才在来的路上 有流浪汉想跟我说话
when that homeless man tried to talk to me on the way in.
麦克斯 这位是蕾拉 事务所另一位合伙人
Uh, Max, this is Leila, another partner at the firm,
还有她夫人 蕾
and her wife, Lei.
她不止是我夫人
She's not just my wife.
还是图片分享网的网红
She's also a star on Instagram.
你看 我也跟别人说你的成就啊
See? I talk about your accomplishments.
我给雕像戴假发
I put wigs on statues
然后从背后给它们拍照
and then photograph them from behind.
就这样吗
That's it?
就这样
That's it.
麦克斯
Max...
你也是律师吗
are you a lawyer too?
不是 但我也曾负责过一两个饮食区[食物法庭]
Uh, no, but I presided over a food court or two in my day.
麦克斯与她的同伴 卡洛琳
Max and her partner, Caroline,
正在筹备开一家甜品吧
are in the process of opening a dessert bar.
她那个"同伴"指的不是情侣的那种
And I don't mean "partner" in the romantic sense.
这部分是我的地盘
I've got that department covered.
欢迎你们 兰迪与麦克斯
Well, welcome, Randy and Max.
我一直希望我们事务所的小团体中
You know, I've been hoping to add another
能多一对异性恋情侣
straight couple to the law firm mix,
但这年头这真是不好找
but, you know, they're so hard to find nowadays.
蕾跟我是在
Lei and I met on an
《女子监狱》的留言板认识的
Orange is the New Black message board.
那留言板有点类似拉拉的约炮软件
It's kind of become the lesbian Tinder.
兰迪 你好像说还有第三个人吗
Uh, Randy, wasn't there rumor of a third?
我一直跟他这么建议
Oh, I keep pitching that,
但他"太爱我一个人"
but he "likes me too much."
抱歉 我又没懂
Again, don't quite get it.
吃了药有些晕
Little hazy.
我得去告诉大厨 因为他就准备了
Well, I'll have to tell the chef he's preparing
六人份的蚝泡
oyster foam for six.
抱歉什么"蚝泡"
I'm sorry, "Oyster foam"?
蚝的泡沫吗
Foam from an oyster?
听起来就"好吃"啊
That sounds delicious.
我知道你所认为的高级料理
I know your idea of fine dining
是芝士火腿馅饼
is a ham and cheese Hot Pocket,
但我真的很高兴你能来
but I am really glad you came.
这位是列宁
Oh, here's Lenin.
兰迪 麦克斯 这位是列宁
Um, Randy, Max, this is Lenin.
他是这里的厨师 也是我爱人
He's the chef. And my lover.
我们也啪啪啪啊
We have sex too.
我跟蕾是"后性爱"
Lei and I are "post sex."
各种亲密 但是不"进出"
All intimacy, no penetration.
等会我将会上七道禽类主题的餐点
I'll be serving a meal of seven bird-themed courses,
每一道都含有独特的飞行幻想
each one it's own unique flight of fancy.
不是我的话 是咯咯笑的帅哥名主播说的
Not my words, a very giggly Anderson Cooper.
在我们开始前 你们两个人
Now, before we begin, do either of you
有对任何食物过敏吗
have any food allergies?
就一种东西 禽类
Just one, birds.
我也不懂她
I don't get her, either.
大家请坐
Let's all sit.
麦克斯
Max.
你为什么想要我坐得远离桌子
Why do you want me to sit that far from the table?
这是有礼的举动
That's me being polite.
你们这趟绝对不枉此行
You are in for such a treat.
列宁是个真正的艺术家
Lenin is a real artist.
屁点儿大又好吃的小料理
teeny-tiny, delicate little meals,
所以房租都得我来付
which is why I pay our rent.
我们第一道菜是法国佳肴
Our first course is a French delicacy.
鸟名为"圃鹀" 烤熟了 可整只吃
The Ortolan Bunting bird, roasted and eaten whole.
抓住它的头 从脚部开始吃吧
Just grasp the bird by its head and start eating at the feet.
好好享受 肯定的
Enjoy. Obviously.
真是"等不及"把那鸟脚放进我嘴里呢
Can't wait to get that bird foot in my mouth.
麦克斯 乳鸽跟耗泡如何
How's the baby pigeon and oyster foam, Max?
太好吃了
Oh, delicious.
真没想到鸟宝宝也能让人这么饱
It's amazing how full babies can make you.
别拍了 蕾 拍太多我吃泡沫的照片了
No, Lei, way too many photos of me eating foam.
我就像口吐白沫的狂犬病狗
Like a rabid dog.
太好了 是这里
Oh, good. This is it.
刚才我敲错门 开门的人
The guy who opened the other apartment door
没穿裤子
wasn't wearing pants.
也没穿内裤
Or underwear.
也没有割包皮
Or was circumcised.
我到了
Hi! I'm here.
我错过[没懂]什么了
What did I miss?
我们看过的每一部电影的中心思想
The point of literally every movie we see together.
玛丽莎 这是卡洛琳 麦克斯的生意伙伴
Marissa, this is Caroline, Max's business partner.
她发过短信说她会来
She texted she was coming.
她通常不会这么大汗淋漓
She's usually not covered in this much sweat.
抱歉 我是跑步跑过大桥
Sorry, I had to run across the bridge,
因为公共自行车需要有信用卡才能租用
'cause you need a credit card for one of those city bikes.
如果我都有信用卡了
Um, if I had a credit card,
我为毛还要骑自行车啊
why would I be riding a damn bike?
我来到"喙" 姐又时尚了
I'm at Beak. I'm trendy again!
第五道菜
Fifth course.
小嘈杂薮鸟配蕨菜
Tiny poached noisy scrubbird with fiddle ferns
外加皮蛋
and fermented egg.
听起来就好恶心 一定很好吃
Oh, that sounds so gross. I bet it's great.
麦克斯 吃啊
Max, eat.
会的会的
I sure will.
小时候看卡通崔弟鸟时
When I used to watch Tweety Bird,
我一直都是想着"它一定很好吃"
all I could think was, "God, that looks delicious."
你已经做得很好了
You're doing great.
谁要再来点酒
Who wants some more wine?
我猜麦克斯想要
I'm guessing Max.
真不敢相信我们在这里
I can't believe we're here,
吃着最上等的... 他说这是啥鸟
eating the finest... what'd he say this was?
冠蓝鸦吗
Blue jay?
你不为我骄傲吗
Aren't you proud of me?
我成功撑过了四道菜[门课]呢
I got through the first four courses.
我高中都没撑过这么多门课
That's more courses than I finished in high school.
瞧瞧这做作
Oh, look at this pretentious,
故意随意摆放的大餐巾
deliberately relaxed large napkin.
真是让人又爱又恨
Love it and hate it.
那是什么
What is that?
前面四道菜
This first four courses!
跟在高中一样 我作弊了
I cheated, like in high school!
我吃不下去 太恶心了
I couldn't eat it; it's gross.
不 你给墨西哥卷饼店那家伙65美分
No, gross is when you hand the guy at Del Taco
让他给你的惊喜 那才叫"恶心"
65 cents and tell him to surprise you.
你居然因为我不愿吃每周六上午
You are judging me for not eating most of my
我爱看的卡通人物而批评我
Saturday morning cartoon lineup?
你想咬一口大公鸡莱亨吗
You want to chomp down on Foghorn Leghorn?
当像兰迪这么棒的男人为了你而搬来纽约
When a great guy like Randy is moving to New York for you,
你必须硬着头皮 把你童年的最爱吃下去
yes, you have to eat your childhood favorites!
谁先过来看怎么把小喇叭鸟
Anyone like to come see the de-spining
的脊椎抽掉吗
of the tiny trumpeter bird?
这没准会让我粉丝突破一百万
This could push me over a million followers.
我吃不下去 卡洛琳
I can't eat that, Caroline.
现在我也没有地方塞了
And I have nowhere to put it.
我的胸罩已经超载了
My bra is at crazy capacity.
消防员都要因为场地太满 把我左乳踢走了
The fire marshal almost kicked out my left boob.
你为何不能直接尝一口呢
Why can't you just try it?
你嘴里肯定塞进过更恶心的东西
You've had worse things in your mouth.
他是为了你搬来这里
He's moving here to be with you.
他是为了工作搬来这里
He's moving here for a job.
听着 无论接下来是什么
Look, whatever comes next,
都给我塞进嘴巴里 吃掉它
just put it in your mouth and eat it.
我都不知道那只鸟还是活生生的
Well, I did not know the bird was gonna be alive.
最糟糕的部分是 跟它对视
Worst part? Making eye contact.
奶油泡菜
Creamed kimchi
鹈鹕舌头配亚洲梨
and pelican tongue with Asian pear.
请享用
Enjoy.
你至少可以吞下一小条舌头吧
The least you can do is swallow a little tongue.
吞舌头 嘴沾白沫
Tongue swallowing? Foam?
这不是餐厅 这是吸毒过量
This isn't a restaurant; it's a heroin overdose.
我爱你
I love you.
好样的 麦克斯
Good for you, Max!
这才是真正的成长
This is real growth.
我感觉那舌头也在品尝我 是不是不太好啊
Is it bad I feel like the tongue is tasting me back?
麦克斯 你在冒汗
Max, you look sweaty.
就像你试图算数时一样
Like when you try to do math.
我觉得那舌头正在我体内寻找出口
I think that tongue is looking for an exit.
兰迪 我们十分兴奋你能与我们一起共事
Randy, we're really excited for you to come work with us.
你能多快速搬来纽约
How fast can you move to New York?
那也比不上我去厕所的速度快
Not as fast as I have to get to that bathroom.
失陪了
Excuse us,
我们得去下小麻雀的房间
we have to go to the little sparrow's room.
不用了 没事 虚惊一场
Nope, it's cool, false alarm.
不 是真的 超级无敌真
Nope, real alarm. Very real alarm.
-要我跟你进去吗 -不用
- Should I come in with you? - No!
甚至连我自己都不想进去
Even I don't want to go in there!
我怀疑这门不隔音 所以你讲话大声点
I doubt this door is soundproof, so talk loud.
先从你正常的音调开始
Just start with your normal volume,
然后再小声一点 就是大声了
and then dial it down a notch.
玛丽莎
Oh, Marissa!
快告诉我
You have to tell me
这些漂亮的玻璃杯在哪儿买的
where you found these fabulous glasses.
是新复古品牌A
Restoration Hardware?
还是美式现代品牌B
Crate and Barrel?
抑或新复古现代品牌C
Restoration Hardware Modern?
贵版宜家D 年轻现代E
West Elm? CB2?
还是无品牌F 没有一个中的吗
CB3? Is there one of those yet?
要不 我们放点音乐吧
You know what? Let's get some music going!
放那种特别大声的电子乐
Like some really loud dubstep,
因为我要喘不上气了
'cause I'm running out of breath.
这里不让放音乐
Oh, there's no music allowed here.
这样我们就听不到品尝食物时
It would get in the way of hearing
口中的交响曲了
the symphony of taste.
听别人说的
Not my words.
好吧 其实是我自己说的
Okay, they were my words.
我想举杯致敬
I think I'd like to make a toast.
不 拜托不要这样做
Oh, no, please don't make a toast.
我已经开始不喜欢你了
I've begun not to like you.
说真的 列宁
Seriously, Lenin.
连轻柔的钢琴曲都不行吗
Not even a little light piano?
又不是让你做多费劲的事
You don't need to reinvent the freaking wheel here.
卡洛琳 拜托 快坐下
Hey, Caroline, please. Just sit.
我找找看还有没有镇静剂
You know what, I see if I have another Klonopin.
-我不需要 -不是给你的
- I'm fine. - It's not for you.
卡洛琳
Caroline.
我该进去看看吗
Should I go in there?
因为我没听见标准的那套
'Cause I am not hearing the standard
嘘嘘声和洗手声
tinkle and a hand wash.
不 别动 坐着就好
No, don't move. Stay there.
那噪音只是水管有点堵而已
That noise is just the pipes backing up a little.
非常堵
Well, a lot.
上帝啊
Oh, Lord!
年轻人嘛
They're young.
我得进去拍
My camera needs to be in there.
不要拍了
Enough with the camera!
你也要搭理下我这个活物吧
I'm alive!
麦克斯
Max.
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
离开这里
Anywhere but here!
麦克斯 别闹了
Max, seriously!
里面到底什么状况
What's going on in there?
里面一切都好
Everything's okay in here!
我们马上出去
We'll be out in a minute.
如果不让我进去 那至少也...
If you're not gonna let me in, at least...
麦克斯
Max!
等等
Wait up!
你无需在我面前觉得丢脸
You don't have to be embarrassed in front of me.
我见过更糟的
I've seen worse.
好吧 我没有
Okay, no I haven't.
你走开啦
Just go away!
我受不了你那个悲哀的表情
I can't take that sad look.
上次栗宝把屎拉在沙发上
It's the same look you gave Chestnut
你也是这个表情
that time he crapped on the couch.
我一个人能行 你不用跟出来
I'm fine alone; you didn't have to leave.
不 我必须出来
No, I did.
他们一定认为那不可能是
They couldn't possibly think one person
一个人的呕吐量
was responsible for all that.
再说了 我不想扔下你
Plus, I don't want to leave you.
你不舒服
You're sick.
比不舒服严重多了
I think it's beyond sick.
我把骨质都吐出来了
I lost bone mass in there.
我现在鞋子都嫌大了
My shoes are too big now.
真是好丢脸啊
I'm so embarrassed!
这是常有的事
Hey, it happens.
你肚子疼而已
You got a stomach ache.
你只是不习惯吃有钱人吃的食物
You're just not used to rich food.
我不习惯有钱人的任何玩意
I'm not used to rich anything.
如果兰迪的世界是这样...
And if this is Randy's world...
鸟骨头和做作的人们
uh, bird bones and pretentious people...
那或许我的身体在告诉我 我接受不了
then maybe my body is telling me I can't take it.
麦克斯 如果我能习惯在便利店买耳环
Max, if I got used to buying earrings at the AMPM,
那你也能习惯精美的食物 做作的人们
you can get used to fancy food and pretentious people.
你不明白
You don't get it!
他是为了我才搬来这里
He is moving here for me.
是哦 你也这么觉得吗
Oh, do you think so?
真希望你的好闺蜜
I wish your best friend
在过去两天有跟你一直念叨这件事
had been telling you that for two days.
他要把他整个人生搬来这里
He's moving his whole life.
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know how to do that.
就连他给我搬椅子时 我都不知道该作何反应
I didn't even know how to react when he moved my chair for me.
你说得对 这无关食物
You were right, it's not about the food;
这事关我们的未来
it's about our future,
而我刚吐了我们的未来一脸
and I just vomited all over our future.
干嘛
What?
我很不想这么说 但你需要来一颗薄荷糖
I hate to say this, but you need a mint.
抱歉 我爱你 但你需要来一颗薄荷糖
Sorry, I love you, but you need a mint.
我需要消失
I need to disappear.
你觉得希拉·纽曼[新生]这名字怎么样
What do you think of the name Sheila Newman?
麦克斯
Max!
兰迪
Randy.
太棒了 正好赶上看我跳下去
Great, just in time to see me jump.
怎么回事 你们去哪儿了
What happened? Where'd you go?
我太快跳上自行车
Oh, I jumped on that bike so fast,
我的"兄弟们"再也不会跟我说话了
my man parts are no longer talking to me.
她不舒服 不想被你看见
She didn't want to be sick in front of you.
你不舒服吗
You got sick?
好啦 我们都听见了
Okay, fine, we all heard it.
但你为什么一句话不说就走了
But why did you leave without saying something?
因为话语是唯一一样
Because words were the only thing
不会从我嘴巴出来的东西
not coming out of my mouth.
麦克斯
Max?
你不看着我吗
You're not gonna look at me?
我不能
I can't.
等等 给
Wait, here.
现在她能了
Now she can.
你最好快回去
You better get back there.
我不想你失去这份工作
I don't want you to lose that job.
我不想要这份工作
I don't want that job.
我都不知道玛丽莎吃了多少药
I don't know how many more pills Marissa took,
但她晕倒在一锅清蒸蛤蜊里
but she passed out in a pot of clam steam.
我错过了清蒸蛤蜊吗
I missed clam steam?
杂志上老提他做的清蒸蛤蜊
I've been reading about his clam steam.
拜托不要再说"清蒸蛤蜊"
Please stop saying "clam steam."
我都可以闻得到这四个字的味儿了
I can actually smell the words.
好吧 麦克斯
Okay, Max.
你又开始面如菜色了
You are starting to turn green again,
要不你坐上来 我会骑自行车送你回家
so why don't you hop on, and I will ride you home
像个爷们一样载你
on my bicycle like a real man.
我不知道 兰迪
I don't know, Randy.
一顿饭的时间 很多东西涌上来
A lot of stuff came up for me at that dinner.
我不止是说
And I'm not just talking about
我今年吃过的每一样东西
every single thing I ate this year.
或许我不适合你
I mean, maybe I'm not right for you.
今晚的事 你别太苛责自己了
Don't be so hard on yourself about tonight.
你看我
I mean, look at me.
我也没有勇气去你打工的餐厅吃饭啊
I'm not brave enough to eat in that diner.
过来
Come here, you.
或许再等60秒会更好
Maybe wait another 60 seconds.
我知道我们不一样
I think we are different.
但我们也算合拍
But we kind of go together.
就像撒胡椒的幼鸟膀胱和香蒜酱
Like peppered baby bird bladder and pesto.
完蛋了 完蛋了
Oh, no. Oh, no.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我要吐了
That's gonna do it!
今晚开敞篷车真是中了"大奖"啊
Wrong night to be driving a convertible.
等等 别跳别跳
Oh, wait... no, no, no, no, no, no.
你第一个餐厅汉堡如何啊
So how's your first diner burger?
还不错
It's not bad.
好像有吃到什么
I'm getting a little something.
豆子吗[跟蚊子谐音]
Um... mesquite?
是啊 他们被灭蚊器弄死
Yeah, they die in the fan
然后尸体掉到了烤肉架上
and then fall on the grill.
我宁愿吃蚊子汉堡也不吃鹈鹕
I'll take mosquito burger over pelican any day.
真有意思 兰迪
Interesting, Randy.
有两名服务员在专心服务你
You get two waitresses paying attention to you
而大多数人一个都没有
and most people get none.
就像那边那个
Like that one over there,
还有那边 以及那边那个男士
over there, and that gentleman over there
等得不耐烦 都要走了
who's just giving up and leaving.
行了 阿憨 我们去吧台边上
Fine, Han, we will go over to the counter
继续聊天了
and continue to talk.
我知道我老说你
I know I say a lot of stuff about you,
尤其爱当面说你
especially to your face,
但谢谢你昨晚的帮忙
but thank you for your help last night.
我知道你也会为我做同样的事
I know you would have done the same thing for me.
但如果我有这么不舒服
But if I ever get that sick,
我准许你杀了我
you have my permission to kill me.
当你走进那间厕所 为我找掉了的耳环时
I mean, when you went into that toilet, looking for my earring,
我就知道我找到了我的后性爱伴侣
I knew I had found my post-sex partner.
你居然为她这么做吗
You did that for her?
一直以来 我们在寻找完美的一对
And all this time, we've been looking for
给我们孩子当干爹妈
the perfect couple to be godparents,
而她们就在我们眼皮底下
and they're right under our noses.
女女干妈妈
Girl-on-girl godparents.
我喜欢
I like it.
你们俩姑娘一定能跟我宝宝好好相处
You two girls are gonna be great with the baby.
我是说 卡洛琳
I mean, Caroline,
你半只胳膊伸进去掏麦克斯的呕吐物
you were elbow-deep in Max's upchuck.
我亲爹我都不会愿意为他这么做
I mean, I wouldn't even do that for my own father
当时他吞下了所有的蜜蜂
when he swallowed all those bees.
苏菲 这真是对我莫大的夸奖
Wow, Sophie, this is such a huge compliment.
虽然是夹在一个可怕的个人回忆里面
Tucked away in a terrible personal memory.
如果我们俩出了什么事
Well, if something would ever happen to us,
让麦克斯来喂奶
let Max do the breast feeding.
因为我可不想我的小孩饿死
'Cause, yeah, I don't want the kid to starve.
这真让人兴奋
This is exciting!
兰迪 我要当干爹啦
Randy, I'm gonna be a godfather.
同样让人兴奋的是
And equally as exciting,
我也要从那个厕所的窗户爬出去啦
I'm gonna be climbing out of that bathroom window
就在差不多两分钟后开爬
in about two minutes.